- feat: Enhance irs_mv with additional crime and drug details, and add a new LLM-based drug extraction script.
- fix(ETL): Correct standardize_units weight and volume calculations to prioritize extracted units over drug_form fallbacks
- fix(ETL): Drop accused_id from insert to pass foreign key constraints and update Pydantic missing name fallback
- fix(ETL): Resolve standardizer logic and float overflow constraints
- fix(ETL): Resolve constraints check_has_measurements and Pydantic string validation for missing LLM extractions
- added db schema
- fix(ETL): Convert LLM confidence extraction percentage (95) to float ratio (0.95)
- feat: Add LLM-powered ETL pipeline for extracting and standardizing drug brief facts, including new data models and schema updates.
- feat: Add drug seizure data extractor with new models for standardized units and seizure worth, and include a test file.
- confused
- -- Both should return 0 SELECT COUNT(*) FROM public.brief_facts_drug WHERE LOWER(TRIM(primary_drug_name)) = 'unknown'; SELECT COUNT(*) FROM public.brief_facts_drug WHERE LOWER(TRIM(drug_name)) = 'unknown';
- Refactor drug standardization statistics for clarity and accuracy
- Refactor code structure for improved readability and maintainability
- feat: Implement LLM-based accused facts extraction, a new core LLM service, and its documentation, alongside updating the gitignore for Python artifacts.
- Update LLM model configurations for extraction tasks and enhance LLM service integration
- Refactor code structure for improved readability and maintainability
- Remove all .env files from tracking
- Merge branch 'main' of https://github.com/ASHISH-RATNA-DARLA/DOPAMS-ETL
- my modified changes
- Initial commit
